[{"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Name the actor who starred in the 2007 drama movie There Will Be Blood.", "correct_answer": "Daniel Day-Lewis", "incorrect_answers": ["Kevin Spacey", "Sean Penn", "Keanu Reeves"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Which of these cigarette brands is produced by Philip Morris International?", "correct_answer": "All of these", "incorrect_answers": ["LM", "Marlboro", "Parliament"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "What were the dodos closest living relatives in nature?", "correct_answer": "Pigeons", "incorrect_answers": ["Chickens", "Parrots", "Turkeys"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Jaguars appearance seems to vary across regions and habitats. How do forest jaguars differ from the jaguars in open areas?", "correct_answer": "Forest jaguars are generally darker and smaller", "incorrect_answers": ["Forest jaguars are generally darker and larger", "Forest jaguars are generally and more spotted", "Forest jaguars are generally larger and lighter in fur color"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "What were the Bosss henchmens names in Lucky Number Slevin?", "correct_answer": "Elvis  Sloe", "incorrect_answers": ["Sloe  Gin", "Mr. Goodkat  Sloe", "Elvis  Costello"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Ann has $5.00 and Jeff gives her $2.50, then she goes and buys $3.38 worth of candy. How much money does she have left?", "correct_answer": "$4.12", "incorrect_answers": ["$3.92", "nothing", "$5.00"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "In the treatment of what disease are the leaves and bark of the guava used?", "correct_answer": "All of these", "incorrect_answers": ["Dysentery", "Cancer", "Diabetes"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "The Cave of Melissani is among the most popular geological landmarks of which Greek island?", "correct_answer": "Kefallonia", "incorrect_answers": ["Lefkada", "Mykonos", "Samos"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Alchemists were in search of \u2018panacea\u2019. What is panacea?", "correct_answer": "Remedy for all ailments", "incorrect_answers": ["The meaning of life", "The Holy Grail", "A piece of Jesus Christ\u2019s cross"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "What was the name of the nurse, portrayed by Julianna Margulies, who attempted suicide in the first season of ER?", "correct_answer": "Carol Hathaway", "incorrect_answers": ["Malik McGrath", "Wendy Goldman", "Lily Jarvik"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "The state of Louisiana is bordered by the Gulf of Mexico on the south and three states. Which state does NOT border Louisiana?", "correct_answer": "Oklahoma", "incorrect_answers": ["Texas", "Arkansas", "Mississippi"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "What actress portrayed Sally in the 1989 romantic comedy movie When Harry Met Sally...?", "correct_answer": "Meg Ryan", "incorrect_answers": ["Kim Basinger", "Melanie Griffith", "Daryl Hannah"]}]